http://www.innerbonding.com/show-page/96/privacy-policy.html

HomeStart HereFreeFree AssessmentFree 7 Day CourseFree & Member ArticlesRelationshipsSelf Improvement: Personal GrowthSpirituality: Spiritual GrowthParentingAddictionForeign LanguagesAll ArticlesFree HelpRelationshipsPersonal DevelopmentParentingSpiritual ConnectionAddictionVideosAboutWhat is Inner Bonding?Who Benefits?6 StepsFoundersSuccess StoriesOutbound LinksPress RoomAffiliate InformationTestimonialsPrivacy PolicyTerms of ServiceCoursesLove Yourself: A 30-Day At-Home IB ExperienceThe Ultimate Collection: Complete Self-LoveThe Power to Heal YourselfWildly Deeply Joyously in LoveUnlocking Your Inner WisdomAttracting your Beloved: A 30-Day At-Home CoursePassionate Purpose, Vibrant Health! A 30-Day at home ExperienceThe Inner Bonding Weekend WorkshopIntimate Relationship ToolboxPermanent Weight LossStoreBooksSelfQuestCoursesLoving Yourself: A 30-Day At-Home IB ExperienceThe Ultimate Collection: Complete Self-LoveThe Power to Heal YourselfWildly Deeply Joyously in LoveUnlocking Your Inner WisdomAttracting your Beloved: A 30-Day At-Home CoursePassionate Purpose, Vibrant Health! A 30-Day at home ExperienceThe Inner Bonding Weekend WorkshopIntimate Relationship ToolboxPermanent Weight LosseStoreeBooksInterviewsWebinarsLectures and WorkshopsInterview PackagesLecturesDVDsCDsGifts 'n ThingsView CartEventsWorkshopsIntensivesSupport GroupsWebinarsFacilitatorsWhat is a Facilitator?Phone and Online sessions with Dr. Margaret PaulFind a FacilitatorFacilitator TrainingSelfQuest®MembershipContact Us
Home > Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
What This Privacy Policy Covers
* This policy covers how Inner Bonding treats personal information that Inner Bonding collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Inner Bonding products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
* This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Inner Bonding does not own or control, or to people that Inner Bonding does not employ or manage.
Information Collection and Use
General
* Inner Bonding collects personal information when you register with Inner Bonding and when you use Inner Bonding products. Once you register with Inner Bonding and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
* Inner Bonding uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, and contact you.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
Inner Bonding does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people except under the following circumstances:
We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Inner Bonding's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
We transfer information about you if Inner Bonding is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Inner Bonding will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
Cookies
* Inner Bonding may set and access Inner Bonding cookies,on your computer.
* Inner Bonding uses web beacons to access Inner Bonding cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with Inner Bonding products and services.
* Strictly necessary cookies. These are cookies that are required for you to use the features available on this website. They include, for example, the ability to login and post a comment.
* Analytical/performance cookies. These cookies allow us to recognize, track, and count the number of visitors who come to this website. They also allow us to track broken pages on the website and to count what visitors do when they click through the website.
* Functionality cookies. These cookies allow us to track and remember your preferences for our website. For example, we can personalized content for you, greet you by name and/or remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).
Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences
* You can edit your Inner Bonding Account Information at any time.
* You can delete your account by calling us or emailing us or deleting your credit card.
* We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Inner Bonding service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Inner Bonding Journal, that are considered part of your Inner Bonding account. You may opt out of receiveing any and all emails at any time by un-checking the "send email" option in your profile and also clicking the "unsubscribe" link contained in our emails.
* Information that may not be deleted from the site if requested:
Message Board Postings, Questions and Answers from the Advice Column
Archived Chat Statements, and other similar information.
* Information that we make best efforts to remove from system:
User Account Data, Personals Data, Address Data, Credit Card Data.
Confidentiality and Security
* We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
* Your Inner Bonding Account Information is password-protected.
* In certain areas Inner Bonding uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
* Inner Bonding may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Inner Bonding account.
Password Help
Daily InspirationAre you always busy? Do you have a busyness addiction? Is being busy a way you avoid feelings of loneliness, fear, aloneness, heartbreak, grief or helplessness over others and outcomes? Today, stop the busyness and feel what is happening within. Compassionately embrace whatever painful feelings you discover, then explore them or release them to Spirit.
By
Dr. Margaret Paul
Inner Bonding Products:
Image
Title
Healthy Ways of Managing ConflictBy Dr. Margaret Paul
Beloved Companionship - An Alternative To LonelinessBy By Margaret Paul, Ph.D.
Inner Bonding CoinBy Dr. Margaret Paul
Do I Have To Give Up Me To Be Loved By My Kids?By Drs. Jordan and Margaret Paul
Explore More Inner Bonding
LATEST PUBLIC ARTICLES
Dec-08: Helpless Regarding Others - a Hard Feeling to BearNov-30: "How Do I Ask For What I Need?"Nov-23: Relationships: "Why am I Struggling After All My Healing?"Nov-16: Caretaking Others Prevents You From Knowing Yourself
DAILY INSPIRATION
Are you always busy? Do you have a busyness addiction? Is being busy a way you avoid feelings of loneliness, fear, aloneness, heartbreak, grief or helplessness over others and outcomes? Today, stop the busyness and feel what is happening within. Compassionately embrace whatever painful feelings you discover, then explore them or release them to Spirit.
By
Dr. Margaret Paul
INNER BONDING EVENTS
Inner Bonding Events
02/24/2021 07:30 AM
5-Day Virtual Intensive
Dr. Margaret Paul
All Inner Bonding Events
More About Inner Bonding
Inner Bonding is a proven six-step self-healing process that has been developed and optimized over 30 years by Dr. Margaret Paul, Ph.D. and Dr. Erika Chopich, Ph.D. It’s comprehensive. It’s practical. And it always works when you do it.
Inner Bonding empowers you to self-heal the root causes of anxiety, depression, addictions, failed relationships and many other problems that inhibit your personal and spiritual growth and satisfaction. It teaches you how to love yourself rather than continue to abandon yourself, how to move beyond emotional dependency and attain emotional freedom, and how to heal the underlying control issues stemming from self-abandonment.
Home   |   Start Here   |   About   |   Courses   |   Store   |   Events   |   Facilitators   |   Membership   |   Privacy Policy
|   Terms of Service
Design by Michelle Davies   |   Technology by Durango Computers, Inc.
Copyright Inner Bonding® Educational Technologies, Inc. 1998-2019
